Yes friend, this Motors is seriously
recommended for buying. The target is Rs 922 today. As per the way
Inkar's new launch Ronin is doing well
in the market, it is sharing the market.
CLSA feels that there will be a
positive impact somewhere else, hence it is
recommended to buy it. CLSA has
come out with a report on Hindalco. The target has been cut
but the target is Rs 525, which is the near
market price. You will see 25% on the
website. They feel that the
production growth of Novelis has been very good. The
inspectors who saw the production cost
increasing in the eliminator will probably
support the price because the
energy costs have increased. So
aluminium is an electricity heavy
business where you need more
electricity for production. Somewhere the production
cost is increasing. Hindalco has benefited from this as the
cost is low and the production is
high. Here I Shri Cement,
Jeffrey Cigarette has come there, they are also doing cement sector
after a long time. Today the office
believes that here you should
look at the demand outlook. The management committee
is positive. Inside management, by 2030,
their limit will be  There will be intense capacity and
somewhere the
management is paying a lot of attention to reducing expenditure on green energy and logistics and
somewhere you will see the benefit of that too, Shri Cement
or TVS Motors, Rigton
Jhala